Vonnegut, Bernard; Papers ua902.068
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- State University of New York at Albany, 1957-1997; Undated; 8; 4.22 cubic ft.
  - Grant- "Microphysical Studies of Noctilucent Clouds", 1987-1991 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 7)
  - Grant - ONR "Microphysical Studies of Noctilucent Clouds", Undated (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 8)
  - International Commission an Atmospheric Electricity, 1967-1984 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 9)
  - International Commission an Atmospheric Electricity Nominating Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 10)
  - Journal of Electrostatics Editorial Board, 1972-1990 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation - [RESTRICTED], 1985; 1988-1989 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 12)
  - National Science Foundation - [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 13)
  - National Science Foundation - OSC Flow Device - [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989; Undated (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 14)
  - National Science Foundation- Small Grants for Exploratory Research, 1987; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 15)
  - Office of Naval Research - RPI, 1970 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 16)
  - Project Themis, 1967-1969; 1971-1972; Undated (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 17)
  - Project Themis Quaterly Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 18)
  - Project Themis Quaterly Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 19)
  - Project Themis Annual Summary #1, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 20)
  - Project Themis Annual Summary #2, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 21)
  - Project Themis Annual Summary #3, 1970-1971; 1973; Undated (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 22)
  - Proposal - Department of Desfense, 1982-1983; Undated (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 1)
  - Proposal - "Maintenance of Electric Field Over the top of Thundercloud", 1983-1984 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 2)
  - Proposal - "Modification of the Surface Temperature by an Artificial Cirrus Cloud", 1980 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 3)
  - Proposal - National Science Foundation "Development of Fuel Additives for Use in Internal Combustion Engines to Produce AgI Nuclei, 1970-1975 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 4)
  - Proposal - National Science Foundation "Study of Nucleation Catalysis Using Modified AgI Lattice", 1972-1973 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 5)
  - Proposal - National Science Foundation "Role of Crystal Lattice in Contact Nucleation", 1973-1974 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 6)
  - Proposal - NOSL Experiment Support, 1971-1983 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 7)
  - Proposal - National Science Foundation "Clean-Air Seeding" - [RESTRICTED], 1979; 1981-1983 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 8)
  - Proposal - "The Nature of Lightning Initiation", 1973-1974 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 9)
  - Proposal - Project Themis, 1967-1970 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 10)
  - Proposal - Project Themis, Undated (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 11)
  - Proposal - "Relationship Between Lattice Constants and Nucleation of Silver Iodide", 1971-1972; Undated (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 12)
  - Reprints and Copies of Tornado Articles, 1966 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 13)
  - Report - "Modification of the Surface Temperature by an Artificial Cirrus Cloud", 1980-1983 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 14)
  - Reports - NASA Contract Report 4313, 1990 (Box 4 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 15)
  - Reports - Project Themis, 1968-1969 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 1)
  - Reports - Project Themis, 1969 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 2)
  - Reports - Project Themis, 1970-1972 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 3)
  - Reports - Project Themis, 1973 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 4)
  - The Research Foundation of SUNY 1982 Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 5)
  - Researh Interests, 1974; 1979; Undated (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 6)
  - SDI Research Protests, 1986; 1988 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 7)
  - Search Committee for Director of Atmospheric Science Research Center, 1974-1975 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 8)
  - Search Committee for Director of Research, 1971-1972 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 9)
  - Search Committee for Manager of Inventions and Licenses, 1978-1979 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 10)
  - Solar Heat Storage Research, Undated (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 11)
  - Study Committee for the National Institute of Ecology, 1970-1971 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 12)
  - Tribute to Bernard Vonnegut, 1997 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee - [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 14)
  - University Awards Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 15)
  - University Senate, 1980-1982 (Box 5 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 16)
  - Weather Modification Experiments, 1971-1978 (Box 6 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 1)
  - Weather Modification Experiments, Undated (Flat-file 7)
  - Weather Modification Information Facility and Archives, 1968-1970; Undated (Box 6 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 2)
- Meetings and Conferences, 1949-1996; Undated; 9; 3.6 cubic ft.
  This series contains records for professional conferences and meetings arranged and/or attended by Dr. Vonnegut as well as project proposals, reports, correspondence, travel arrangements, conference programs, meeting agendas, registrations and other conference-related items, press release, and records on the classes he taught. Additionally, this series includes papers written by others that Dr. Vonnegut found interesting or pertinent to his research.
  - Adirondack Conference on Atmospheric Nuclei, 1957 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 1)
  - Adirondack Conference on Electrostatics, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 2)
  - Air Force Cambidge Research Laboratories Scientific Balloon Symposium, 1963 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 3)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science December Meeting, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 4)
  - American Chemical Society Sigma Xi talk, 1980 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 5)
  - American Geophysical Union 48th Annual Meeting, 1967 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 6)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1980 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 7)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1981 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 8)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1982 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 9)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 10)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1984 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 11)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1985 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 12)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1986 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 13)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1987 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 14)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 15)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1992 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 16)
  - American Geophysical Union Fall Meeting, 1996 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 17)
  - American Geophysical Union Spring Meeting, 1979 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 18)
  - American Geophysical Union Spring Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 19)
  - American Geophysical Union Spring Meeting, 1986 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 20)
  - American Geophysical Union Spring Meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 21)
  - American Meteorological Society 23rd Conference on Radar Meteorology and Conference on Cloud Physics, 1986 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 22)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers Speciality Conference Ocean Egineering III, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 23)
  - Annual Meeting of the Wilderness Medical Society, 1989 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 24)
  - Brooklyn Polytechnic Colloquium, 1984 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 25)
  - Christmas Chemical Engineering Symposium on Nucleation, 1951 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 26)
  - Clarkson University Physics Colloquium, 1984 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 27)
  - Conference on Electrostatics of the American Meteorological Society, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 28)
  - Conference Programs, 1949-1951 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 29)
  - Conferences in Tallinn Estonian SSR, USSR and Budapest, Hungary, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 30)
  - Conference in Uppsala, Switzerland and Paris, France, 1985 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 32)
  - Department of the Interior Bureau of Reclamation Nucleation Conference, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 33)
  - Eighth Conference Inadvertent and Planned Weather Modification, 1981 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 34)
  - Eighth International Conference on Atmospheric Electricity, 1984; 1987-1988 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 35)
  - Eighth International Conference on Cloud Physics, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 36)
  - Electrostatics Society of America, 1970-1975 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 37)
  - Electrostatics Society of America 17th Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 38)
  - Electrostatics Society of America Conference on Electrostatics, 1983 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 39)
  - European Geophysical Society 15th General Assembly, 1990 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 40)
  - Fourth International Conference on the Universal Aspects of Atmospheric Electricity, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 41)
  - Fifth International Conference on Atmospheric Electricity, 1971; 1973-1974 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 1)
  - Fourth Technical Conference - Ashbury Park, New Jersey, 1950 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 2)
  - Indiana University Medical Center of Sigma Xi Talk, 1982 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 3)
  - International Centre for Theoretical Physics Autmn Workshop on Cloud Physics and Climate, 1984-1986 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 4)
  - International Centre for Theoretical Physics Second Autumn Workshop on Cloud Physics and Climate, 1984; 1987 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 5)
  - International Commission on Atmospheric Electricity International Workshop on Global Atmospheric Electric Measurements, 1989 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 6)
  - International Conference on Atmopheric Electricity, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 7)
  - International Conference on Cloud Physics, 1965 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 8)
  - International Conference on Cloud Physics, 1968 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 9)
  - International Geophysical Year, 1955-1958 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 10)
  - International Union of Geodesy and Geophysics General Assembly, 1967 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 11)
  - International Union of Geodesy and Geophysics 21st General Assembly, 1995 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 12)
  - International Workshop on Light Scattering by Irregular Shaped Particles, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 13)
  - Irish Meterological Society Talk, 1986 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 14)
  - Lightning and Static Electricity Conference, 1972 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 15)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory Workshop on Links Between Variations in Solar Activity, Atmospheric Conductivity and Clouds, 1975-1976; 1996 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 16)
  - Marshall Space Center Lecture, 1974 May (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 17)
  - Meetings, 1954-1955 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 18-19)
  - Meetings, 1956-1958 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 20-21)
  - Meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 22-23)
  - Meetings, 1959 (Box 2 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 24-25)
  - Meetings, 1960 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 1)
  - Meetings, 1961 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 2)
  - Meetings, 1962 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 3)
  - Meetings, 1963 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 4)
  - Meetings, 1964 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 5)
  - Middle Atmospheric Workshop, 1977; 1986; Undated (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 6)
  - MIT Visiting Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 7)
  - NASA Atmospheric Processes Research Review FY-80, 1980 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 8)
  - NASA Atmospheric Processes Research Review FY-81, 1981 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 9)
  - NASA Atmospheric Processes Research Review FY-82, 1982 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 10)
  - NASA Atmospheric Processes Research Review FY-83, 1983 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 11)
  - NASA Atmospheric Processes Research Review FY-84, 1984 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 12)
  - NASA Atmospheric Processes Research Review FY-85, 1985 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 13)
  - NASA Mesoscale Atmospheric Processes Research Program Review, 1985 May (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 14)
  - NASA Symposium on Lightning Technology, 1978; 1980 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 15)
  - NASA Workshop on Current Scientific Issues in Large Scale Atmospheric Dynamics, 1985 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 16)
  - NASA Workshop on the Need for Lightning Observations from Space, 1971; 1978-1979 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 17)
  - NASA Workshop on the Role of Electrodynamics of the Middle Atmosphere on Solar Terrestrial Coupling, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 18-19)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research Advisory Panel, 1970; 1972-1973 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 20)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research Meeting, 1982 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 21)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research Workshop on Airborne Instrumentation, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 22)
  - National Hill Suppression Project, 1965-1966 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 23)
  - Naval Research Laboratory Lightning Phsyics Review Panel, 1987 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 24)
  - Naval Research Laboratory Workshop, 1964-1965; 1983 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 25)
  - New York State Section American Physical Society Fall Meeting, 1983 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 26)
  - Ninth International Conference on Atmospheric Electricity, 1989; 1992 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 27)
  - Office of Naval Research Conference on Solar-Terrestrial Effects on the Lower Atmosphere, 1981 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 28)
  - Presentation, "Research Indicated by Convective Electrification Mechanisms", Undated (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 29)
  - Satellite Workshop, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 30)
  - Second Inadvertent Weather Modification Workshop, 1974 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 31)
  - Seventh Conference on Inadvertent and Planned Weather Modification, 1979 (Box 3 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 32)
  - Sixth International Conference on Atmospheric Electricity, 1971-1982 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 1)
  - Sixth International Conference on Condensation Nuclei, 1966 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 2)
  - Strategic Defense Initative Research Review, 1987; Undated (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 3)
  - Strategic Defense Initiative Research Review, 1989 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 4)
  - Symposium on Electrostatic Effects Associated with Dried Powders, 1967 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 5)
  - Talks, Discussions, Speeches, 1963-1988 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 6)
  - Technical Workshop for the of Laboratory Research and Facilities for Cloud Physics and Chemistry, 1985-1986 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 7)
  - Third Annual Yellowstone Field Research Seminar, 1962-1963 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 8)
  - Third International Conference on Atmospheric and Space Electricity, 1962-1963 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 9)
  - University of Calgary Colloquim Talk, 1980-1981 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 10)
  - University on Michigan Seminar on Meteorology, 1967 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 11)
  - Visit to Polish Academy of Sciences, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 12)
  - Visit to China an Taiwan, 1980-1991 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 13)
  - Weather Modification Association Silver Anniversary Meeting, 1976 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 14)
  - Whitecap Workshop, U.C.G., 1975; 1982-1983 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 15)
  - White House Conference on International Cooperation, 1965 (Box 4 (9-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 16)
- Subject Files, 1938-1997; Undated; 10; 7 cubic ft.
  Series 10 contains files on a wide variety of subjects; people, articles, topics in science, and other topics of interest to Dr. Vonnegut throughout his career.
  - A, 1962-1976; 1979-1982; 1985; 1989; 1994 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - AAAS "lonizers", 1980; 1982 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - AAAS: Stored Energy In Water, 1978; 1981 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - All Things C, 1995 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - AM. Geophysical Union, 1963-1969; 1981-1982 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - AM. Geophysical Union, 1990 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Amer, N.M., U.CAL Berkeley, Photoacoustic Spectroscopy, 1978-1981 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - BAMS "Errors" Column (AMS), Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - AMS, 1959-1969; 1973; 1976; 1981; 1990 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Arnold, Roy Misc., 1975-1976; 1980; 1982; 1984 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Arnold, Stephen, Brooklyn Polytech, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - ASRC Electrostatics Bibliography Conference, 1971 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - ASRC Director, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - ASRC Misc., 1967-1986; 1988; 1990 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15-16)
  - ASRC Pub No's, 1969-1970; 1972 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - ASRC Visit, Electrostatics Facility, 1972 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - B, 1958-1995 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19-20)
  - Baker, Marcia, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Baller, Paul S., 1966-1967; 1969; 1972 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Balloon Program, 1982-1984; 1986 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Time Lapse Photography from Balloons, 1957; 1970; 1976-1977 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Barchet "Other Seeding Agents & Alternatives to Silver Iodide, 1977 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Barreto, 1969; 1977-1987 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 26-27)
  - Tankers (Re: Barreto), 1968; 1970-1971 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Bentley, W.A., 1977-1979 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Bjornsson, S., 1966-1970 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Blanchard, 1938-1996 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 31-32)
  - Blau, Henry H, 1963; 1966; 1968-1970; 1973-1974 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Boeck, William L, 1961; 1971-1980; 1984; 1990; 1992 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 34-35)
  - Bowers, 1991 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Breidenthal, R.E, 1985-1987; 1989 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Buechner, W.W., 1968-1969; 1973-1974 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Bullock, J.W, 1965-1969 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - C, 1960-1996 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - C, 1960-1996 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Chapman, Seville (DR), 1954; 1968; 1970-1974; 1976 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Clippings - Bus Crash, Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Cloud Seeding, 1952-1956; 1958; 1961-1967 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Church, C.R, 1970-1971; 1975; 1979-1983; 1995 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Cook, Jim, Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Corrugahorn, 1976 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Crawford, Perry, 1979; 1981-1982 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - D, 1962-1976; 1978; 1980; 1987-1988; 1991-1992 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Da Vinci, Leonardo, 1956 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Derenzo, David R., 1979; 1981-1983; 1988-1989 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Dessens, Henri, 1973 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Detwiler, Andy, 1976-1986; 1988-1991; 1993-1994 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Dewan, Edmond, 1965-1994 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14-15)
  - Dewan's Mystery Cloud, 1985 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Dolezalek, Hans, 1962-1963; 1966-1976; 1980-1981 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Doppler Radar, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - E, 1962-1972; 1978-1979; 1982; 1985-1986; 1990 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - EDC Film, 1966; 1968-1971; 1973 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 20-21)
  - Eden H.F. (Frank), 1966-1968; 1972-1973; 1975-1976; 1987 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - ESPY, 1993 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - F, 1961-1987 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24-25)
  - Film "Atmospheric Electricity", 1960; 1964-1965 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Findeisen Quote, 1950 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - The Franklin Institute 3/18/70, 1969-1971; 1974 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Ben Franklin References, 1952; 1961; 1991-1992 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Fulgurites, 1976 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - G, 1961-1977; 1980-1981; 1985; 1988 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - General Electric - Recruitment Correspondence, 1945; 1947 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 32)